{"data":[{"question":"We were very proud of his ________.","a":"fearful","b":"fearfulness","c":"fearless","d":"fearlessness","answer":"4","explain":"\n- His: used as a possessive determiner followed by a noun ( fearlessness)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The Sloths spend most of ________ time hanging upside down from trees and feeding on leaves and fruit.","a":"its","b":"his","c":"her","d":"their","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The Sloths is plural","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The native people in the Americas were referred to as Indians because according to the ________ at the time, Christopher Columbus had reached the East Indies.","a":"believe","b":"belief","c":"believed","d":"believer","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The + Noun (\u00a0Belief: a strong feeling that something is true )","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"________ missile was used in the war between American and Irak.","a":"Guidance","b":"Guide","c":"Guided","d":"Guideless","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun.\u00a0\n+ When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle.\u00a0\n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"A barometer is a device with a sealed metal chamber designed ________ the changes in the pressure of air in the atmosphere.","a":"to reading","b":"read","c":"reading","d":"to read","answer":"4","explain":"- To: used\u00a0after a verb when you talk about the purposes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Cotton fiber, like other vegetable fibers, ________ composed mostly of cellulose.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (Cotton fiber) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Almost all life depends ________ chemical reactions with oxygen to produce energy.","a":"with","b":"to","c":"on","d":"for","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Depend on sth\/sbd: if something depends on something else, it is directly affected or decided by that thing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"It may be argued that modern presidents have far ________ responsibilities than their predecessors did.","a":"great","b":"more great","c":"greater","d":"most great","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Comparative of adj\/adv.\u00a0\n+ Short adj\/adv: adj\/adv + er + than.\u00a0\n+ Long adj: More + adj\/adv + than.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"She put a (well-) ________ case for increasing the fees.","a":"reason","b":"reasoned","c":"reasonable","d":"reasonably","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Compound adjectives can be formed as follows.\u00a0\n+ Adverb-past participle \/ noun + ed: well-known.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Many grasshoppers can produce sounds by ________ their hind legs against their wings.","a":"rub","b":"to rub","c":"rubbed","d":"rubbing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use V-ing after a preposition (by)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}